A Guide to the Andrew Jackson Montague Papers, 1854-1938
Library of Virginia
- X: Printed Materials, 1842-1937., Extent: 14. (Box 48-61)
  - Business cards for Harvey and Gore, dealers in antique jewelry, London, England, [1924?]. (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Business card for Phyllis Earle, Ltd., hair and skin care, London, England, [1924?]. (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Business card for Anderson and McAuley, Ltd., manufacturers, London, England, [1924?]. (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Sales ticket from Swears and Wells, London, England, [1924?]. (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Equivalent Value of English and American Money,[1924?]. (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Card for Scott and Company, London, England, [1924?]. (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Program leaflet, 150th Anniversary Battle of Lexington,April 1925. (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - The Fifth National Conference on State Parks in the Heart of the Proposed Shenandoah National Park,May 1925. (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - To whom will your Estate go, if you die without a Will?1925. (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Menu for a banquet given in honor of the delegates of the 23rd Conference of the Inter-Parliamentary Union, by the U.S. group at the Mayflower Hotel, Washington, D.C. (2 copies), 6 October 1925. (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Seating list for guests at the banquet given in honor of the delegates of the 23rd Conference of the Inter-Parliamentary Union, by the U.S. group at the Mayflower Hotel, Washington, D.C., 6 October 1925. (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - The Italian Debt Settlement: Message of the President of the United States, Senate document 3, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 8 December 1925. (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - The Italian Debt Settlement: Message of the President of the United States, Senate document 5, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 8 December 1925. (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - The Belgian Debt Settlement: Message of the President of the United States, Senate document 4, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 8 December 1925. (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - The Esthonian [Estonian] Debt Settlement: Message of the President of the United States, Senate document 7, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 8 December 1925. (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - The Latvian Debt Settlement: Message of the President of the United States, Senate document 8, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 8 December 1925. (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - The Czechoslovak Debt Settlement: Message of the President of the United States, Senate document 6, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 8 December 1925. (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - A bill for the relief of Lieutenant James Floyd Terrell, Medical Corps, United States Navy, H.R. 2731, introduced by A. J. Montague, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 7 December 1925. (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - A bill for the relief of Claude S. Betts, H.R. 2636, private calendar number 5, introduced by A. J. Montague, Sixty0-ninth Congress, first session (2 copies), December 1925. (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Money, Honey, Money, words by Sarah Johnson Cocke and music by Edwin Hedden (3 copies), 1925. (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Brochure, Shenandoah National Park in Virginia, Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1925. (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - A Book of Prayers,[1925]. (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Who's Who of the Twenty-Third Conference of the Interparliamentary Union (second edition), 1925. (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - Speakers for Tuesday Evening typed on Congressional letterhead stationary. [1925]. (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Foreign Debt Funding Legislation: Hearings before the Committee on Ways and Means, House of Representatives, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 2 parts, January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - George A. Finch: Communication from the President of the United States, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 4 January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - A bill to authorize the settlement of the indebtedness of the Kingdom of Rumania to the United States of America, H.R. 6772, Union calendar number 14, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Settlement of the Indebtedness of Rumania to the United States: Report, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 7 January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - A bill to authorize the settlement of the indebtedness of the government of the Kingdom of Belgium to the government of the United States, H.R. 6774, Union calendar number 15, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 7 January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Settlement of the Indebtedness of Belgium to the United States: Report, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 7 January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - A bill to authorize the settlement of the indebtedness of the Republic of Esthonia [Estonia] to the United States of America, H.R. 6775, Union calendar number 16, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 7 January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Settlement of the Indebtedness of Esthonia [Estonia] to the United States: Report, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 7 January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - A bill to authorize the settlement of the indebtedness of the government of the Republic of Latvia to the government of the United States of America, H.R. 6776, Union calendar number 17, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Settlement of Indebtedness of Latvia to the United States: Report, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 7 January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - A bill to authorize the settlement of the indebtedness of the Czechoslovak Republic to the United States of America, H.R. 6777, Union calendar number 18, January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Settlement of the Indebtedness of Czechoslovakia to the United States: Report, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 7 January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - A bill to authorize the settlement of the indebtedness of the Kingdom of Italy to the United States of America, H.R. 6773, Union calendar number 22, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Settlement of the Indebtedness of Italy to the United States: Report, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 8 January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Italian Debt Settlement: Speech of Hon. Andrew J. Montague of Virginia in the House of Representatives from the Congressional Record, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 13 January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - European Economic and Political Survey No. 10, Reverence Service on International Affairs, 30 January 1926. (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Virginia's Call must not be Denied: to the Women of the South, reprinted from the Richmond Times-Dispatch, 19 February 1926. (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - A bill granting an increase of pension to Mattie E. Butler, H.R. 12031, introduced by A. J. Montague, Sixty-ninth Congress, first session, 8 May 1926. (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Interparliamentary Union, from Advocate of Peace, July 1926. (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Interparliamentary Bulletin, number 6, November-December 1926. (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - The General Assembly of Virginia, Manual of the Senate and the House of Delegates, session1926. (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Historical Survey of the Rumanian People by N. Banescu, 1926. (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - The Chicago Civic Opera Company, Grand Opera,February 1927. (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - The Constitution of Virginia: Report of the Commission to Suggest Amendments to the Constitution to the General Assembly, March 1927. (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - The Mayflower's Log, volume III, number 1, March 1927. (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Convocation of the XXIVth Conference of the Interparliamentary Union, May 1927. (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - The Gradual and Progressive Codification of International Law by James Brown Scott, reprinted from The American Journal of International Law, volume XXI, number 3 July 1927. (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Union Interparlementaire: XXIV Conférence, Paris 25-30 Août 1927, 1927. (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - XXIVe Conférence Interparlementaire. Paris 25-30 Août 1927. Documents Préliminaires,August 1927. (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Inter-Parliamentary Union: XXIVth Conference, Paris August 25th to 30th, 1927. Preliminary Documents. English Translation,August 1927. (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Menu for lunch, written in French, 3 August 1927. (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Education New and Old: Address Delivered at the Opening of the Academic Year of Columbia University by Nicholas Murray Butler, 28 September 1927. (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - The Lost Art of Thinking: An Address before the Institute of Arts and Sciences, Columbia University by Nicholas Murray Butler, 17 October 1927. (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Advertisement for Rosine Aoust, hats and robes, Paris, France, [1927]. (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Annuaire Interparlementaire,1927. (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Advertisement for Pinaud perfumes and colognes, [1927]. (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Sales slip for G. Gerson with fabric swatch attached, Paris, France, [1927]. (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Inter-Parliamentary Bulletin,1927. (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Advertisement for Levis (2 cards), Paris, France, [1927]. (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Advertisement for Benoit-Lascoumes, Paris, France, [1927]. (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Advertisement for Au Grand Siécle, Art Ancien, Paris, France, [1927]. (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - This Week in Paris,1927. (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - Advertisement for Ch. Blineau, Paris, France, [1927]. (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - card for A. Aldebert & Ses Fils, Paris, France, (5 cards), [1927]. (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Leaflet for English Theatre, Paris, France, [1927]. (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - Card for Maurice Fabricant, Paris, France, [1927]. (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - Sales slip for Grands Magasins du Louvre, Paris, France, [1927]. (Box 56, Folder 47)
  - Inter-Parliamentary Bulletin, seventh year, number 6, November-December 1927. (Box 56, Folder 48)
  - Jackson Day Dinner menu cover, 12 January 1928. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Program, Myra Hess, pianist, and Joseph Szigeti, violinist, performing at the White House, 26 January 1928. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Confederate Veteran, volume XXXVI, number 1, January 1928. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - A bill for the relief of Claude S. Betts, H.r. 4608, private calendar number 269, introduced by A. J. Montague, Seventieth Congress, first session (2 copies), 6 February 1928. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Inter-Parliamentary Bulletin, 8th year, number 2 (2 copies), March-April 1928. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Union Interparlementaire Listes,April 1928. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Advertisement calendar from the Riggs National Bank, May 1928. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - The Monthly Pocket Guide to Rome,May 1928. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Das Berliner Programm: Hotel Esplanade, Berlin, Germany, 21-27 August 1928. (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Cunard Line, Cabin Passenger Service. R.M.S. Scythia sailing from Liverpool to Boston and New York,30 August 1928. (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Dinner in Honor of Benjamin A. Ruffin, President Lions International, by the Richmond Lions Club,26 September 1928. (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Inter-Parliamentary Bulletin, 8th year, number 6, November-December 1928. (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - A bill to provide for the study, investigation, and survey, for commemorative purposes, of battle fields in the vicinity of Richmond, Virginia, H.R. 15655, introduced by A. J. Montague, Seventieth Congress, second session (2 copies), 21 December 1928. (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Pledge cards for the memorial building fund for the Home for Needy Confederate Women (3 copies), 1928. (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Boat schedule between Hamburg, Germany, and New York, New York, written in German, 1928. (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - XXVe Conférence Interparlementaire Berlin, 1928. (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Envelope addressed E. Braun & Co., Wien I Graben 8, Berlin-Karlsbad, 1928. (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Booklet and map titled Pharus-Plan Wien, [1928]. (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - What's Doing in Vienna, also titled in German and French, 1928. (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Child Welfare Extension Service: Hearing before the Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, House of Representatives, Seventieth Congress, second session, 24-25 January 1929. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - calendar advertising Riggs National Bank, January 1929. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - A bil to provide for the study, investigation, and survey, for commemorative purposes, of battle fields in the vicinity of Richmond, Virginia, H.R. 15655, Union calendar number 801, introduced by A. J. Montague, Seventieth Congress, second session (2 copies), 18 February 1929. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Invitation to the inauguration of Herbert Hoover, 4 March 1929. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Inauguration Ceremonies Program,4 March 1929. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - A bill to provide for the study, investigation, and survey, for commemorative purposes, of battle fields in the vicinity of Richmond, Virginia, H.R. 22, introduced by A. J. Montague, Seventy-first Congress, first session (2 copies), 15 April 1929. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Advocate of Peace Through Justice, volume 91, number 4, April 1929. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Calendar advertising the Riggs National Bank, April 1929. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Thank you card from Mrs. A. J. Montague for subscription/advertisement for the charity costume ball benefitting the Home for Confederate Women, May 1929. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Tickets for charity costume ball benefitting the Home for Confederate Women (3 tickets), 4 May 1929. (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Tickets for charity costume ball benefitting the Home for Confederate Women, Patron's Ticket (2 tickets), 4 May 1929. (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Calendar advertisement for the Riggs National Bank, May 1929. (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Calendar advertisement for the Riggs National Bank, June 1929. (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Advertisement for Kinloch in Essex County, Virginia, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac R.R. Company Time Tables,1929. (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - The Black Swan: The Magazine of Virginia, November 1929. (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - In Memory of the Heroes in Gray, published by the Home for Confederate Women, 1929. (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Alpine Summer, 1929, for Boys [and] Girls,1929. (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Catalogue of an Exhibition of Contemporary Portraits at the Virginia House, Virginia Historical Society, 1929. (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - The Cathedral and Metropolitical Church of Christ, Canterbury: a Handbook for Pilgrims,1929. (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Stratford-on-the-Potomac to be purchased by the Robert E. Lee Memorial Foundation: Press Notices and Editorial Comment,1929. (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Map of Rome, Italy, 1929. (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Artistic Guide to Florence and Its Surroundings, 1929. (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Advertisement for Kinloch in Essex County, Virginia, 1929. (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Through Centuries Three, pamphlet advertising book of the same title by David D. Squires, 1929. (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - A bill to authorize the board of visitors of R. E. Lee Camp, No. 1, Confederate Veterans, in its discretion, to admit wives and widows of Confederate veterans into the Confederate Soldiers' Home at Richmond, House bill number 318, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - A Monument of Service to the Undying Memory of the Women of the Southern Confederacy (3 copies), 1929. (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Personal sketch of Andrew Jackson Montague for Who's Who in America, volume 16, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Map of Switzerland, in German, 1929. (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Tour booklet for Geneva, Switzerland, [1929?]. (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Pamphlet for Golay sons & Stahl, watchmakers and jewellers, Geneva, Switzerland, 1929. (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Italy guidebook, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Cosulich Line: Moter Vessels Saturnia and Vulcania, (2 copies), [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Advertisement for Buca di San Ruffillo, restaurant, written in Italian, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Guide to hotels in Italy, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Advertisement for Giacobbe Giuseppe, Venice, Italy, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Advertisement for Olga Asta & c, Venice, Italy, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Guide to Florence, Italy, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - Envelope from Scuola Merletti di Burano, Venice, Italy, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - Guide to Florence, Italy, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - Venice: an Illustrated Guide to Places of Interest with Plans and Map, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - Advertisement for A. Binocesana, Venice, Italy, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - How to See Venice: Map & Guide of Venice,[1929]. (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - The Ducal Palace of Venice, [1929]. (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - Order blank for Register of Members adn Ancestors, Colonial Dames of America (2 copies),. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - A bill to provide for the creation of the Colonial National Monument in the State of Virginia, and for other purposes, H.R. 8424, Seventy-first Congress, second session, 10 January 1930. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Vest Pocket Congressional Directory, Seventy-first Congress, second session, February 1930. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Inter-Parliamentary Union: Circular to the Groups number 3,5 February 1930. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Calendar advertisement for the Riggs National Bank, February 1930. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - House resolution 190, introduced by A. J. Montague, recommending the printing of Lieutenant Colonel H. L. Landers' report concerning the Seven Days' Battles as a document, 24 March 1930. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Calendar advertisement for the Riggs National Bank (5 copies), March 1930. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - James River, Va.: Letter from the Secretary of War, Seventy-first Congress, second session, March 1930. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - A bill to provide for the creation of the Colonial National Monument in the Commonwealth of Virginia, and for other purposes, H.R. 12235, Union calendar number 368, Seventy-first Congress, second session, May 1930. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Order of Memorial Exercises in the House of Representatives,15 May 1930. (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - To Establish a Laboratory for the Study of the Criminal, Dependent, and Defective Classes: Hearings before the Committee on the Judiciary, House of Representatives, Seventy-first Congress, second session, 19 May 1930. (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Statement of the Virginia Historical Society regarding old mansions in Virginia, May 1930. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - 40th Annual Confederate Reunion, Biloxi, Mississippi, June 1930. (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - List of First Class Passengers, S.S. Minnewaska, from New York, Atlantic Transport Line,5 July 1930. (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Complimentary ticket to the Warrenton Pony Show, July 1930. (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Important memorandum regarding the 26th Inter-Parliamentary Union Conference, 21 July 1930. (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Corporation of the City of London Conversazione to Welcome the Delegates to the 26th Inter-Parliamentary Union Conference (4 copies), 21 January 1930. (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Dublin Weekly Programme, Gresham Hotel, Dublin[, Ireland] (2 copies), [1930]. (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Inter-Parliamentary Union 26th Conference Dinner,22 July 1930. (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Program for the Garrick Theatre, Almost a Honeymoon,1930. (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Keith Prowse Programme, guide to the London Theatre, [1930]. (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Calendar advertisement for the Riggs National Bank, July 1930. (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - London Midland and Scottish Railway Company Reservation of Seats, Compartments, and Sleeping Berths,[1930]. (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Information on the Park Lane Hotel, 1930. (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Souvenier Log [of the] Leviathan, United States Lines (2 copies), [1930]. (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Notice from the Riggs National Bank, 1 October 1930. (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - A Confederate Catechism: The War of 1861-1865,1930. (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Your Dowry of Beauty by Dorothy Gray, 1930. (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Creating the Colonial National Monument: Hearings before the Committee on the Public Lands, House of Representatives, Seventy-first Congress, second session (2 copies), 1930. (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - How to See Edinburgh, Glasgow, the Trossachs, Lochs Katrine & Lomond, Melrose, Ayr, etc.,[1930]. (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Advertisement for Gordon's Irish Lace Depot, Dublin, Ireland, [1930]. (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Dublin Ireland's Captial City,[1930]. (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Souvenir from Ireland, Clerys Dublin, Dublin, Ireland, [1930]. (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - Hotel bill, Central Hotel, Glasgow, Scotland, 1930. (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - American Monthly, volume XXIV, number 4, April 1931. (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - Virginia Born Presidents Unveiling of the bust of President Thomas Jefferson, Capitol, Richmond, Virginia, 22 September 1931. (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - Documents Franco Roumains, numbers 3-4, September-October 1931. (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - Union Interparlementaire XXVIIe Conférence, Excursion À Sinaïa, Bucharest, Rumania (3 copies) 4 October 1931. (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Dinner menu, 27th Inter-Parliamentary Union, Bucharest, Rumania, 3 October 1931. (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - Virginia Born Presidents Unveiling of the Bust of President William Henry Harrison, Capitol, Richmond, Virginia, 6 October 1931. (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - Menu in Greek, 1931. (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - Contract Bridge at Sight by Charles True Adams, 1931. (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - Map of Roumania, 1931. (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - Envelope, Wiener Sanatorium, Dr. Anton Loew in Wien, IX/2, Mariannegasse 20, Pelikangasse 5, 1931. (Box 59, Folder 44)
  - Resolved that the historical statements concerning the Seven Days' Battles...be printed, with illustrations and maps, as a document, H. Res. 144, introduced by A. J. Montague, Seventy-second Congress, first session, 13 February 1932. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Calendar advertising the Riggs Natioanl Bank, February 1932. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - George Washington Bicentennial Historical Loan Exhibition at the Corcoran Gallary of Art, including the full length Gilber Stuart portrait of Washington, 5 March 1932. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Calendar advertising the Riggs National Bank, March 1932. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Court of Claims of the United States: R. L. Montague v. the United States,4 April 1932. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Consent of States to Sue United States for Direct Taxes Collected: Hearing before the Committee on the Judiciary, House of Representatives, Seventy-second Congress, first session, 8 April 1932. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Calendar advertising the Riggs National Bank, June 1932. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - In the Court of Claims of the United States: Plaintiff's Motion for a New Trial, Amendment of Findings of Fact, and Rehearing, and Brief in Support Thereof,18 August 1932. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Calendar advertising the Riggs National Bank, August 1932. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Advertisement for the M. W. Locke Shoe, 1932. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Manual of the Senate and House of Delegates: General Assembly of Virginia (3 copies), 1932. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Calendar advertising the Riggs National Bank, February 1933. (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace: Executive Committee minutes of meeting,23 February 1933. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Consent of States to Sue United States for Direct Taxes COllected: Report, Seventy-second Congress, second session, 1 March 1933. (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - A bill for the Relief of Captain Arthur S. Bell, Officers' Reserve Corps, H.R. 4451, introduced by A. J. Montague, Seventy-third Congress, first session (2 copies), 29 March 1933. (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Our Ship of State: an address delivered at the Parish Art Museum, Southampton, L.I., by Nicholas Murray Butler, 3 September 1933. (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Calendar advertising Tabb, Brockenbrough & Ragland Insurance, 1933. (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Nominating Ballot for the Woman's National Democratic Club, 1933. (Box 60, Folder 18)